Mohawk Airlines Records
Mohawk Airlines Records
1948-1967
Mohawk Airlines.
48.0 linear ft.
Company founded in 1945 as Robinson Airlines Corporation; name changed in 1952. Headquarters: Ithaca, N.Y. Collection includes legal files, correspondence, clippings, press releases, statistics, financial records, reports.
149317
Biographical History
Mohawk Airlines began operations in 1945 as Robinson Airlines out of Ithaca, New York. In 1948 its headquarters relocated to Utica, New York, and the name was changed to Mohawk Airlines in 1952 when the company was purchased by Robert Peach. Mohawk Airlines operated in the Mid-Atlantic region of the United States, primarily in New York and Pennsylvania, from the mid-1940s until its acquisition by Allegheny Airlines in 1972; at one point it also experimented with helicopter airline service to the Adirondacks.
At its height, the company employed over 2,200 people. The company pioneered several technical and social aspects of regional airline operations, including being the first airline in the United States to hire an African American flight attendant (1958), the first airline to use a centralized computer-based reservation service (1961), and the first regional airline to utilize flight simulators (1965).
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Mohawk Airlines Records consists of legal files, publicity, statistical files, financial files, bound reports, general files, and miscellaneous. There are no employee records in the collection.
Legal files relate to various cases, incidents, events, and issues; the material includes briefs, petitions, motions, testimony, reports, applications, and other forms of legal data. Publicity includes newspaper clippings, news releases, newsletters, advertising, and information bulletins. Statistical files contains assorted statistics such as passenger load and airport activity. Financial files includes bound and unbound financial statements and operating forecasts. Bound reports concern various aspects of the business, including station traffic, traffic flow analyses, schedules, and so on. General files consists of financial forecasts and marketing department material. Miscellaneous material includes books, films, and general information on local service airlines and helicopter airlines.
Arrangement of the Collection
Legal files are subdivided by the identification number assigned by Mohawk Airlines and are in chronological (?) order. Publicity, general files, and miscellaneous are arranged alphabetically by type of material. Statistical files, bound reports, and financial files are in no particular order.
Subject and Genre Headings
Business and Industry; New York State; Mohawk Airlines -- Archives.; Robinson Airlines Corporation -- Archives.; Aeronautics, Commercial -- Law and legislation.; Aeronautics, Commercial -- United States.; Airlines -- United States.; Airlines -- Management.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Legal files.; Press releases.; Reports.; Statistics.; Aeronautics.; Transportation.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Legal files
  - 18322
    - New York State Department of Transportation New England / Great Lakes Service Investigation (Box 1)
    - Northeast Airlines New England / Great Lakes Service Investigation (Box 1)
    - Trans-East Airlines New England / Great Lakes Service Investigation (Box 1)
    - Mohawk Airlines New England / Great Lakes Service Investigation, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Mohawk Airlines New England / Great Lakes Service Investigation, Vol.s 1 and 2, 4 folders (Box 1)
    - Mohawk Airlines New England / Great Lakes Service Investigation, Rebuttal (Box 2)
    - Mohawk Airlines New England / Great Lakes Service Investigation, Testimony (Box 2)
    - States of New Hampshire and Vermont New England / Great Lakes Service Investigation (Box 2)
    - Northern New England / Great Lakes Service Investigation
      - Miscellaneous
        - Orders (Box 2)
        - Notices (Box 2)
        - Correspondence (Box 2)
        - Information and Notes (Box 2)
      - Petitions for an Investigation (Box 2)
      - Petitions for Leave to Intervene (Box 2)
      - Motions for Consolidation (Box 2)
      - Answers to Motions to Consolidate (Box 2)
      - Motion for Leave to file Unauthorized Document (Box 2)
      - Motion for Leave to file Late Documents (Box 2)
      - Answers to Petitions to Expand the Issues (Box 2)
      - Petitions for Reconsideration of Order E-24916 (Box 2)
      - Answers to Petition for Modification of Order E-24916 (Box 2)
      - Initial Decision of the Examiner (Box 2)
      - Report of Prehearing Conference (Box 2)
      - Exceptions and Objections to Report of Pre-hearing Conference (Box 2)
      - Statements of Issues (Box 2)
      - Motion to Postpone Preceeding (Box 2)
      - Answer to Motion to Postpone (Box 2)
      - Statements of Position (Box 2)
      - Motion of Mohawk for Submission of Further Evidence (Box 2)
      - Petition for Discretionary Review (Box 2)
      - Answer to Petition for Discretionary Review (Box 2)
      - Motion for Clarification of Order Board (Box 2)
    - Consolidated cases
      - Application of Keene (et al.) for Service between Maine, Vt., N.H. and Albany, Syracuse, Cleveland, Detroit, Ohio (Box 2)
      - Application of Mohawk for certificate amend. for service in Order E-24916 (Box 2)
      - Application of Northeast Airlines for certificate of public convenience and necessity (# 18431) (Box 2)
      - Application of Northeast Airlines of public convenience and necessity (# 18432) (Box 2)
      - Application of Statewide Airlines # 16333 (Box 2)
      - Motion for Consolidation # 16333 (Box 2)
      - Petition of Statewide to operate as air taxi and certified air carrier #18767 (Box 2)
      - Answer to Application of Statewide #18767 (Box 2)
      - Motion of AL for leave to File Answer (Box 2)
    - Exhibits
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 2)
      - GRTR. BTV Indust. Corp. and the BTV-Lake Champlain Chamber of Commerce (Box 2)
      - City of Cleveland and Cleveland Chamber of Commerce (Box 3)
      - Detroit Aviation Commission, GRTR, DTW, Board of Commerce, etc. (Box 3)
      - MDA of Syracuse and Onondaga County (Box 3)
      - State of Maine and Bangor (Box 3)
  - 19201
    - Briefs
      - Allegheny Airlines, 2 folders (Box 3)
      - City of Columbus, Ohio and Chamber of Commerce G (Box 3)
      - Greater Cincinnati Chamber of Commerce and Kenton City Airport Board (Box 3)
      - County of Westchester (Box 3)
      - Frontier Airlines (Box 3)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 3)
      - Ozark Airlines (Box 3)
      - Port of New York Authority (Box 3)
      - Town of Greenwich (Box 3)
      - United Airlines (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Orders (Box 3)
      - Notices (Box 3)
      - Correspondence (Box 3)
      - Reference Material (Box 3)
      - Motion for Expansion of Order (Box 3)
      - Motion to File Unauthorized Reply (Box 3)
      - Motions to Consolidate Applications (Box 3)
      - Petitions for Reconsideration and Clarification of Order E-26711 (Box 3)
      - Answers to Petitions for Reconsideration of Order E 25913 and Motions to Consolidate (Box 3)
      - Statements of Issues, etc. (Box 3)
      - Information Responses (Box 3)
      - Prehearing Conference Report (Box 3)
      - Exceptions to Prehearing Conference Report (Box 3)
      - Petitions for Leave to Intervene (Box 3)
      - Initial Decision (Box 3)
      - Exceptions to Examiners Decision (Box 3)
      - Charts for Oral Argument (Box 3)
      - Motion to Correct Transcript (Box 3)
      - Petition for Reconsideration, Rehearing, and Argument (Box 3)
      - Application of Mohawk Airlines Docket 19366 (HPN-west) (Box 3)
      - Application of Mohawk Airlines, Docket (Iship-west) (Box 3)
      - Application of Allegheny Airlines (East to White Plains) (Box 3)
      - Application of Allegheny Airlines (Midwest to White Plains) (Box 3)
      - Application of Braniff Airways (Box 3)
      - Application of City of Bridgeport (#16696) (Box 3)
      - Application of Columbus and Columbus Chamber of Commerce Docket 19281 (Box 3)
      - Application of Frontier Airlines (Box 3)
      - Application of Ozark Airlines (Docket 19286) Application of TransWorld Airlines (Docket 19290) (Box 3)
      - Application of Trenton and Mercer County (Box 3)
    - Exhibits
      - Allegheny Airlines (Box 3)
      - American Airlines (Box 3)
      - Testimony, City of Fort Smith (Box 3)
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 3)
      - Greater Cincinnati Chamber of Commerce and Kenton County Airport Board (Box 4)
      - City of Saint Louis and Chamber of Commerce (Box 4)
      - County of Westchester, New York (Box 4)
      - Civil Aeronautics Board (Box 4)
      - Frontier Airlines (Box 4)
      - Eastern Airlines (Box 4)
      - Islip; Long Island (Box 4)
      - Mohawk Airlines, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Northwest Airlines (Box 4)
      - Ozark Airlines (Box 4)
      - Town of Rye, New York (Box 4)
      - Town of Greenwich, Conn., 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Transworld Airlines (Box 4)
      - United Airlines (Box 4)
  - 16474
    - Orders (Box 5)
    - Notices (Box 5)
    - Statement of Issues and Responses (Box 5)
    - Report of Prehearing Conference (Box 5)
    - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 5)
    - Petitions for Leave to Intervene (Box 5)
    - Answers re: Petitions for Leave to Intervene (Box 5)
    - Petition of Allegheny for Reconsideration of Order E-22629 (Box 5)
    - Answers re: Petition of American Airlines for Reconsideration of Order E-22629 (Box 5)
    - Motions to Consolidate (Box 5)
    - Answers to Motion to Consolidate (Box 5)
    - Petitions for Review of Order E-23106 (Box 5)
    - Petitions for Consideration of Order E-23175 (Box 5)
    - Answers re: Petitions for Consideration of Order E-23175 (Box 5)
    - Petition of Pilgrim Aviation and Airlines to Maintain Status Quo of Allegheny SVC (Box 5)
    - Motion for Partial Dismissal (Box 5)
    - Answers re: Motion for Partial Dismissal (Box 5)
    - Motion of American Airlines to Strike Exhibits of Mohawk (Box 5)
    - Answer of Mohawk to Motion of American to Strike Exhibits (Box 5)
    - Motion to Expand Issue and Reopen Proceeding (Box 5)
    - Answers re: Motion to Expand Issue and Reopen Proceeding (Box 5)
    - Petition for Review of Initial Decision (Box 5)
    - Answers re: Petition for Review (Box 5)
    - Testimony of the County of Warren (Box 5)
    - Material Presented at Oral Argument (Box 5)
    - Petitions for Reconsideration of Order # E-25847 (Box 5)
    - Answer to Petition for Reconsideration of Order E-25847 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence and Miscellaneous Related Data (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous Information and Notes (Box 5)
    - Application and Amendment of American Airlines for Renewal of Its Certification for Segment 8 (# 15496) (Box 5)
    - Application of American Airlines for Amendment to extend Segment 8 beyond Islip, N.Y. to HPN and Albany (#16693) (Box 5)
    - Application of American Airlines to Amend Certification by adding HPN as an interpoint (#14976) (Box 5)
    - Application of American Airlines to alter point of origin or term re: Flts. Service. PVD, NYC, EWR (#14381) (Box 5)
    - Application of Bridgeport for Service between Bridgeport-Buffalo with interpoints (#16676) (Box 5)
    - Application of Mohawk to serve Islip, N.Y. DTT with other interpoints (#16439) (Box 5)
    - Application of Town of Islip to serve L.I. Airport, Albany, Syracuse, Rochester and Buffalo (# 16015) (Box 5)
    - Application of New Castle for amended certification for Piedmont Aviation (# 16699) (Box 5)
    - Application of New Castle for amended certification for Lake Central (#16698) (Box 5)
    - Application of New Castle for amended certification for Mohawk Airlines (# 16697) (Box 5)
    - Application Mohawk for Delayed Inauguration at Bridgeport and Islip (Box 5)
    - Application of Mohawk for amendment of certification to serve Albany, 11PN, DCA (#14923) (Box 5)
    - Exhibits
      - American Airlines (Box 5)
      - Baltimore, Maryland (Box 5)
      - City of Bridgeport (Box 5)
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 5)
      - State of Connecticut (Box 5)
      - Eastern Airlines (Box 5)
      - Empire State Airlines (Box 5)
      - Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 6)
      - Rebuttal Exhibits (Box 6)
      - Islip, Long Island (Box 6)
      - Massachusetts Port Authority (Box 6)
      - Allegheny Airlines Inc. Segment 8 Renewal and Route Realignment Investigation, April 1, 1966; May 20, 1966; 2 folders (Box 6)
      - New Castle County Airport Commission (Box 6)
      - City of New Haven, Connecticut and the Greater New Haven Chamber of Commerce (Box 6)
      - New York Airways (Box 6)
      - New York State Department of Commerce (Box 6)
      - City of Philadelphia (Box 6)
      - Pilgrim Aviation and Airlines, Inc. (Box 6)
      - Trenton, N.J. Bureau of Aeronautics (Box 6)
      - City of Westchester (Box 6)
      - State of Vermont (Box 6)
      - City of Albany, and Albany Chamber of Commerce (Box 6)
      - Allegheny Airlines (Box 6)
      - American Airlines (Box 6)
      - City of Bridgeport (Box 6)
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 6)
      - Mohawk Airlines, Inc. (Box 6)
      - City of Philadelphia (Box 6)
      - Pilgrim Aviation and Airlines (Box 6)
      - Schenectady Chamber of Commerce (Box 6)
      - State of Vermont, Vermont Chamber of Commerce (Box 6)
      - County of Westchester, N.Y. (Box 6)
      - County of Warren (Box 6)
  - 17436
    - Briefs
      - Allegheny Airlines (Box 7)
      - Allentown, Bethlehem, Easton (Box 7)
      - American Airlines (Box 7)
      - Baltimore and State Aviation Commission of Maryland (Box 7)
      - City of Bridgeport (Box 7)
      - City of Cleveland and Chamber of Commerce of Cleveland (Box 7)
      - Eastern Airlines (Box 7)
      - City of Erie and Erie Municipal Airport Authority (Box 7)
      - Town of Islip (Box 7)
      - Lake Central Airlines, Inc. (Box 7)
      - Mohawk Airlines, Inc. (Box 7)
      - New Haven Parties (Box 7)
      - Northwest Airlines, Inc. (Box 7)
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 7)
      - Port of New York Authority (Box 7)
      - Tri-State Airport Authority and GTR Huntington Area Chamber of Commerce (Box 7)
      - TWA (Trans World Airlines) (Box 7)
      - United Airlines (Box 7)
      - United States Court of Appeals (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous Data
      - Orders (Box 7)
      - Notices (Box 7)
      - Correspondence (Box 7)
      - Answer to Petition Mohawk for Show Cause Order (Box 7)
      - Motion to Consolidate (Box 7)
      - Petitions for Leave to Intervene (Box 7)
    - Consolidated Cases
      - Application of Lake Central Airlines Docket 19329 (Box 7)
      - Application of Mohawk for Certificate Amendment (Box 7)
      - Application of Mohawk (Box 7)
    - Exhibits
      - Allegheny Airlines
        - Testimony (Box 7)
        - Rebuttal (Box 7)
        - Testimony (Box 7)
        - Rebuttal (Box 7)
        - Direct Exhibits (Box 7)
      - Allentown-Bethlehem-Easton Airport (Box 8)
      - American Airlines (Box 8)
      - Baltimore (Box 8)
      - City of Bridgeport, Conn. (Box 8)
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 8)
      - State of Connecticut (Box 8)
      - Detroit Aviation Commission, Board of County Road Commissioners, Greater Detroit Board of Commerce (Box 8)
      - Eastern Airlines (Box 8)
      - Erie, Pa. (Box 8)
      - Islip, L.I. (Box 8)
      - Lake Central Airlines (Box 8)
      - Mercer County and City of Trenton, New Jersey (Box 8)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 8)
      - New Haven, Connecticut (Box 8)
      - New York State (Box 8)
      - Northwest Airlines (Box 8)
      - Parkersburg and Marietta Chambers and City of Parkersburg (Box 8)
      - Transworld Airlines (Box 8)
      - Tri-State Authority and Greater Huntington Area Chamber of Commerce (Box 8)
      - United Airlines (Box 8)
  - 11620
    - Briefs
      - Bureau of Economic Regulation (Box 8)
      - Eastern Airlines, Inc. (Box 8)
      - National Airlines (Box 8)
    - Orders
      - Prehearing Conference Report, Exceptions and other Miscellaneous Data (Box 8)
      - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 8)
      - Motions and Petitions re: Reconsideration of Order #E-18470 (Box 8)
      - Answers re: Motions and Petitions for Reconsideration of Order #E-18470 (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous Answers to Miscellaneous Motions and Petitions (Box 8)
  - 14041
    - Briefs
      - Allegheny Airlines, Inc. (Box 9)
      - City of Bradford, Pa. (Box 9)
      - Bureau of Economic Regulation (Box 9)
      - City of Jamestown, New York (Box 9)
      - Liberty Airport Authority (Box 9)
      - Mohawk Airlines, Inc. (Box 9)
      - City of Olean, New York (Box 9)
      - State of New York (Box 9)
    - Orders
      - Petitions for Review of Initial Decision (Box 9)
      - Answers to Petitions for Review of Initial Decision (Box 9)
      - Motion to Amend Order E-18820 and to Consolidate (Box 9)
      - Answers to Motion to Amend Order E-18820 and to Consolidate (Box 9)
      - Motion of Mohawk to Strike Portion of Brief of City of Olean, New York and Answer of Olean (Box 9)
      - Petition of Olean for Reconsideration and Answers re: Same (Box 9)
      - Motion to Reopen Record and Answers re: Same (Box 9)
      - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 9)
    - Exhibits
      - Allegheny Airlines (Box 9)
      - Bureau of Economic Regulation (Box 9)
      - Bradford, Pa. (Box 9)
      - Jamestown, New York (Box 9)
      - Liberty Airport Authority (Box 9)
      - Mohawk Airlines, Inc. (Box 9)
      - New York State Department of Commerce (Box 9)
      - Olean, New York (Box 9)
      - Oneonta, New York (Box 9)
  - 13494
    - Reopened Data
      - Orders (Box 9)
      - Notices (Box 9)
      - Proposed Statement of Issues (Box 9)
      - Petition for Investigation (Box 9)
      - Motions for Consolidation (Box 9)
      - Answers re: Motions for Consolidation (Box 9)
      - Report of Prehearing Conference Excerpts (Box 9)
      - Motion to Terminate (Box 9)
      - Answers re: Motion to Terminate (Box 9)
      - Motion to Dismiss (Box 9)
      - Answers re: Motion to Dismiss (Box 9)
      - Petitions for Reconsideration of Order Dismissing Investigation (Box 9)
      - Correspondence (Box 9)
      - Notes, Reference Data (Box 9)
      - Responses, Exhibits
        - Allegheny (Box 9)
        - Eastern Airlines (Box 9)
      - Orders (Box 9)
      - Notices (Box 9)
      - Petitions for Leave to Intervene (Box 9)
      - Motions to Include and/or Consolidate (Box 9)
      - Answers to Motions to Include and/or Consolidate (Box 9)
      - Notice of Prehearing Conference (Box 9)
      - Prehearing Conference Report (Box 9)
      - Exceptions to Prehearing Conference (Box 9)
      - Report Statement of Position (Box 9)
      - Motion to Correct Transcript (Box 9)
      - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 9)
      - Petitions For Review of Initial Decision (Box 9)
      - Answers to Petitions for Review of Initial Decision (Box 9)
      - Oral Argument Material Presented By the Various Companies (Box 9)
      - Brief to Examiner
        - Laconia, N.H. (Box 10)
        - State of New Hampshire (Box 10)
        - Rutland, Vermont (Box 10)
        - State of Vermont (Box 10)
        - Allegheny Airlines (Box 10)
        - Eastern Airlines (Box 10)
        - Mohawk Airlines (Box 10)
        - Northeast Airlines (Box 10)
        - Bureau of Economic Regulation (Box 10)
        - New Haven, Connecticut and Chamber of Commerce (Box 10)
        - Stratford, Conn. (Box 10)
        - Lewiston-Auburn, Maine (Box 10)
        - State of Maine (Box 10)
        - Lawrence, Mass. (Box 10)
      - Exhibits
        - New Hampshire Aeronautics Commission (Box 10)
        - City of Laconia, New Hampshire (Box 10)
        - State of New Hampshire (Box 10)
        - City of Newport, Vermont (Box 10)
        - Massachusetts Port Authority (Box 10)
        - Allegheny Airlines (Box 10)
        - Eastern Airlines (Box 10)
        - Mohawk Airlines (Box 10)
        - Northeast Airlines (Box 10)
        - Bureau of Economic Regulation (Box 10)
        - City of New Haven, Connecticut (Box 10)
        - Town of Houlton, Maine (Box 10)
        - Portland, Maine Chamber of Commerce (Box 10)
        - Cities of Lewiston and Auburn, Maine (Box 10)
        - State of Maine, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - City of Lawrence, Mass. (Box 11)
        - New England Council, Boston, Mass. (Box 11)
  - 11614
    - Petitions for Reconsideration, Rehearing or Reargument (Box 11)
    - Answers re: Petitions for Reconsideration, Rehearing, or Reargument (Box 11)
    - Reply of American Airlines to Answer of Mohawk to Petitions for Reconsideration (Box 11)
    - Motion of American Airlines for Leave to File Unauthorized Document (Box 11)
    - Correspondence (Box 11)
    - Briefs
      - Elmira/Corning Area (Box 11)
      - Allegheny (Box 11)
      - Bureau of Economic Regulation (Box 11)
      - New York State Department of Commerce (Box 11)
      - Harrisburg Area Chamber of Commerce (Box 11)
      - City of Philadelphia and Philadelphia Chamber of Commerce (Box 11)
      - United (Box 11)
      - City of Williamsport and Williamsport Municipal Airport (Box 11)
    - Orders and Notices (Box 11)
    - Petitions and/or Motions for Reconsideration and Consolidation (Box 11)
    - Answers re: Petitions and/or Motions for Reconsideration and Consolidation (Box 11)
    - Petitions for Leave to Intervene (Box 11)
    - Statement of Corning Glass Works in opposition to United Airlines Application (Box 11)
    - Prehearing Conference Report (Box 11)
    - Objections to Prehearing Report (Box 11)
    - Motion by Mohawk to Withhold from Public Disclosure (Box 11)
    - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 11)
    - Petitions for Discretionary Review (Box 11)
    - Answers re: Petitions for Review of Initial Decision (Box 11)
    - Motion for Enlargement of Time and Right to Open and Close (Box 11)
    - Answer to Motion for Enlargement of Time and Right to Open and Close (Box 11)
    - Oral Argument Data (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous Data (Box 11)
    - Exhibits
      - New York State Department of Commerce (Box 11)
      - United (Box 11)
      - Philadelphia, Pa. Chamber of Commerce (Box 11)
      - Harrisburg, Pa. Chamber of Commerce (Box 11)
      - Williamsport, Pa. Civic Party (Box 11)
      - Allegheny (Box 11)
      - Bureau of Economic Regulation (Box 12)
      - Elmira Area (Box 12)
  - 13527
    - Briefs
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 12)
      - United Airlines (Box 12)
    - Brief to Examiner
      - Allegheny Airlines (Box 12)
      - American Airlines (Box 12)
      - Broome County (Box 12)
      - Lackawanna and Luzerne Counties (Box 12)
      - New York State Department of Commerce (Box 12)
      - Williamsport Municipal Airport Authority and City of (Box 12)
      - Trans World Airlines (Box 12)
    - Orders and Notices (Box 12)
    - Joint Application, TWA/MOH/AAL (Box 12)
    - Filings re: Scranton/Wilkes-Barre, Pa. (Box 12)
    - Petitions for Reconsideration of Order E-18834 (Box 12)
    - Answers to Mohawk's Motion for Reconsideration of Order E-18334 (Box 12)
    - Motions to Consolidate and/or Expand Issues (Box 12)
    - Answers to Motions to Consolidate and/or Expand Issues (Box 12)
    - Prehearing Conference Report and Exceptions to Same (Box 12)
    - Statement of Position (Box 12)
    - Answers re: Motion to Reopen Hearing (Box 12)
    - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 12)
    - Petitions for Review of Initial Decision (Box 12)
    - Answers to Petitions for Review (Box 12)